Guide to the John T. Davis Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
John T. Davis Accessions
1980-2010
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Davis, John T. (John Terry), 1955-
UPWC.10133
30 Linear Feet
29 boxes
Multiple accessions from music writer, John T Davis include a wide expanse of Davis's articles from 1980-2010, including articles from Davis's music column in the Austin-American Statesman and extensive subject files. Also present are numerous files from SXSW and ACL, as well as manuscript drafts and other materials relating to Davis's book, Austin City Limits: 25 Years of Music.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts of John T. Davis, 2010, 2019
Biographical / Historical
John T. Davis is a prolific writer who has covered the music, personalities and culture of Texas and the Southwest for a variety of regional, state and national publications. His byline has appeared in the Austin American-Statesman, the Austin Chronicle, Texas Monthly, Texas Highways, San Antonio magazine, Men's Journal, No Depression, Billboard and Newsday and the website Culturemap.com. He is also a frequent contributor to Austin Monthly, Austin Woman and other regional publications and websites. He has been interviewed by VH-1, CMT and NPR and has appeared in the documentary film Lubbock Lights.
He is the author of the book Austin City Limits: 25 Years of American Music and has assisted in the preparation and editing of several other volumes, including biographies of musicians Jerry Jeff Walker and Johnny Bush, and a travel guide to Texas.
In 2011, he co-authored Thin Slice of Life, a mystery novel published in 2012 by Stephen F. Austin University Press. He and his co-authors (writing as "Miles Arceneaux") published a sequel, La Salle's Ghost, in October 2013, followed by a third volume, Ransom Island, in 2014, North Beach, in 2015, and the latest addition to the series, Hidden Sea, in 2017.
In 2014, his biography of the musical group The Flatlanders was published by University of Texas Press. In 2016, he contributed a chapter to the Texas A and M Press anthology, Pickers and Poets: The Ruthlessly Poetic Singer-Songwriters of Texas. During 2017-2018, he served as the editor of the online newsletter for the Texas Dance Hall Preservation non-profit.
[From Author's website]
Abstract
Multiple accessions from music writer, John T Davis include a wide expanse of Davis's articles from 1980-2010, including articles from Davis's music column in the Austin-American Statesman and extensive subject files. Also present are numerous files from SXSW and ACL, as well as manuscript drafts and other materials relating to Davis's book, Austin City Limits: 25 Years of Music.
Index Terms
Subjects
Music; Journalism; Popular music -- Writing and publishing
Subjects (Persons)
Davis, John T. (John Terry), 1955-
Subjects (Corporations)
Austin city limits (Television program)
- Accession 2010-133
  Abstract
  Newspaper articles, SXSW and ACL programs, and drafts for the John T. Davis archive. This collection includes a wide expanse of Davis's articles from 1980-2010, including articles from Davis's music review column in the Austin-American Statesman. This collection also contains official SXSW and ACL music and program guides, as well as drafts of Davis's comprehensive ACL book, Austin City Limits: 25 Years of Music.
  - "General Articles", 1980-2009
    - Picnic, 1980 (Box 1925, Folder 1)
    - Austin-American Statesman Clips (3 folders), 1983-1984 (Box 1925, Folder 2-4)
    - Austin-American Statesman Clips (2 folders), 1985 (Box 1925, Folder 5-6)
    - Austin-American Statesman Clips, 1985-1986 (Box 1925, Folder 7)
    - Austin-American Statesman Clips (2 folders), 1986-1987 (Box 1925, Folder 8-9)
    - Austin-American Statesman Clips, 1987 (Box 1925, Folder 10)
    - "Bonnie Raitt #1, Bonnie Raitt #2", September 4, 1989 (Box 1925, Folder 11)
    - July-August 1991 (Box 1925, Folder 12)
    - November-December 1991 (Box 1925, Folder 13)
    - "1990 Chronicle Stories, 1991 Too" (Box 1925, Folder 14)
    - January-February 1992 (Box 1925, Folder 15)
    - September-October 1992 (Box 1925, Folder 16)
    - December 1992 (Box 1925, Folder 17)
    - January 1993 (Box 1925, Folder 18)
    - February 1993 (Box 1925, Folder 19)
    - March 1993 (Box 1925, Folder 20)
    - March-April 1993 (Box 1925, Folder 21)
    - April 1993 (Box 1925, Folder 22)
    - May 1993 (Box 1925, Folder 23)
    - June 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 1)
    - July 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 2)
    - August 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 3)
    - September 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 4)
    - October 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 5)
    - November 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 6)
    - December 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous clips, 1993 (Box 1926, Folder 8)
    - January 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 9)
    - February 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 10)
    - March 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 11)
    - SXSW Johnny Cash Preview, March 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 12)
    - April 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 13)
    - May 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 14)
    - June 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 15)
    - July 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 16)
    - August 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 17)
    - September 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 18)
    - October 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 19)
    - November 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 20)
    - Album reviews, November 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 21)
    - Austin-American Statesman features, November 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 22)
    - December 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 23)
    - Austin-American Statesman features, December 1994 (Box 1926, Folder 24)
    - January 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 25-26)
    - February 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 27)
    - March 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 28)
    - "Rosalyn", March 7, 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 29)
    - "Rosalyn, Guy Clark", April 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 29)
    - April 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 30)
    - May 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 31)
    - June 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 32)
    - July 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 33)
    - August 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 34)
    - "20 year column", August 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 35)
    - September 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 36)
    - October 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 37)
    - November 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 38)
    - December 1995 (Box 1926, Folder 39)
    - January 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 40)
    - February 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 41)
    - March 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 42)
    - April 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 43)
    - May 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 44)
    - June 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 45)
    - July 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 46)
    - August 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 47)
    - September 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 48)
    - October 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 49)
    - November 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 50)
    - "Best of '96", December 1996 (Box 1926, Folder 51)
    - January 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 52)
    - February 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 53)
    - March 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 54)
    - "Abra Moore Review", March 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 55)
    - April 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 56)
    - May 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 57)
    - June 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 58)
    - July 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 59)
    - August 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 60)
    - September 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 61)
    - October 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 62)
    - November 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 63)
    - December 1997 (Box 1926, Folder 64)
    - January 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 1)
    - February 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 2)
    - March 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 3)
    - April 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 4)
    - May 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 5)
    - June 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 6)
    - July 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 7)
    - August 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 8)
    - September 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 9)
    - October 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 10)
    - November 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 11)
    - December 1998 (Box 1927, Folder 12)
    - February, 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 13)
    - March 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 14)
    - April 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 15)
    - May 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 16)
    - June 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 17)
    - July 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 18)
    - September 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 19)
    - October 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 20)
    - November 1999 (Box 1927, Folder 21)
    - Articles from 1980-1999 (2 folders) (Box 1927, Folder 22-23)
    - January 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 24)
    - February 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 25)
    - March 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 26)
    - April 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 27)
    - May 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 28)
    - June 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 29)
    - July 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 30)
    - August 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 31)
    - September 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 32)
    - October 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 33)
    - November 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 34)
    - Articles from 2000 (Box 1927, Folder 35)
    - "2001 Articles" (Box 1927, Folder 36)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2001 (Box 1927, Folder 37)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2002 (Box 1927, Folder 38)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2003 (Box 1927, Folder 39)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2004 (Box 1927, Folder 40)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2005 (Box 1927, Folder 41)
    - Unsorted Articles (2 folders), 2006 (Box 1927, Folder 42-43)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2007 (Box 1928, Folder 1)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2008 (Box 1928, Folder 2)
    - Unsorted Articles, 2009 (Box 1928, Folder 3)
    - Articles, undated (Box 1928, Folder 4)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 1928, Folder 5)
    - "Austin Sun, River City Sun, Rumors Articles" (Box 1928, Folder 6)
    - "Misc. Statesman Clips" (Box 1928, Folder 7)
    - "Misc. Chronicle Copy" (Box 1928, Folder 8)
    - "Texas Hwy. Stories, ACL, Marathon" (Box 1928, Folder 9)
    - "Misc. Magazine Copy" (Box 1928, Folder 10)
  - "Kathy Mattea" [2 Microcassette Tapes] (Box 1928, Folder 11)
  - "Bridges" Microcassette Tape (Box 1928, Folder 12)
  - "Angela" Microcassette Tape (Box 1928, Folder 13)
  - "Willie II at Pedernales Studio for NARM" Microcassette Tape, February 18, 1993 (Box 1928, Folder 14)
  - "Marcia/Grdb" Microcassette Tape (Box 1928, Folder 15)
  - "Mandy, Lucinda: Lorne, Tequilafest" Microcassette Tape, August 1992 (Box 1928, Folder 16)
  - "Folver" Microcassette Tape (Box 1928, Folder 17)
  - "2 Storage Set A" and "2 Storage Set B" [3 Floppy Discs] (Box 1928, Folder 18)
  - Drafts of Johnny Bush Biography (2 folders) (Box 1928, Folder 19-20)
  - Whiskey River (Take My Mind) on Johnny Bush (Box 1928, Folder 21)
  - "Day of the Deed, Nov. 2" Draft (Box 1928, Folder 22)
  - "Chapter Eleven" Draft, January 23, 2008 (Box 1928, Folder 23)
  - "Chapter Two" Draft (Box 1928, Folder 24)
  - "Carlito's Last Resort" Draft, June 4, 1994 (Box 1928, Folder 25)
  - "Original Clips" (Box 1928, Folder 26)
  - "Insight Texas Travel Guide Copy" (Box 1929, Folder 1)
  - "Carlito's Last Resort" Draft (2 folders), August 30, 1991 (Box 1929, Folder 2-3)
  - "Third Coast Clips, Also Billboard, Duede" (Box 1929, Folder 4)
  - "Chronicle, Austin Light Stories, Rumors Stories, Austin Sun Stories" (Box 1929, Folder 5)
  - "Talon; LBS Obit" (Box 1929, Folder 6)
  - Various Research (Box 1929, Folder 7)
  - "Rumors Articles" (Box 1929, Folder 8)
  - "Lubbock, Sharon [Ely] / Jo Harvey [Allen]" and "Joe [Ely] / Sharon [Ely] 1-7: Re: Butch [Hancock]" and "Butch 10-22" Microcassette Tapes (Box 1929, Folder 9)
  - Binder of News Clippings (Box 1929, Folder 10)
  - Notes on Awhile Back (Box 1929, Folder 11)
  - "Misc. Clips" (Box 1929, Folder 12)
  - "The Fat Master/Piece" Novel Project, 1988-2009 (Box 1929, Folder 13-14)
  - "2010 Statesman Articles" (Box 1929, Folder 15)
  - Notes on "Rome Inn" and "Willie [Nelson]—7/20" (Box 1929, Folder 16)
  - Austin Lifestyle, September/October 2010 (Box 1929, Folder 17)
  - Notes on Johnny Bush Attractions and Transcripts, February 20, 2003 (Box 1929, Folder 18)
  - Notes on Johnny Bush Press Releases (Box 1929, Folder 19)
  - "Johnny Bush" Tape Transcripts (Box 1929, Folder 20)
  - "Bush—One Generation Back From E-mail Draft", February 22, 2003 (Box 1930, Folder 1)
  - "Bush—Proof" (2 folders) (Box 1930, Folder 2-3)
  - Assorted Newspaper Articles (Box 1930, Folder 4)
  - "Bastrop Book Project" (Box 1930, Folder 5)
  - "Austin Music Memorial" (Box 1930, Folder 6)
  - "LBJ" (Box 1930, Folder 7)
  - Austin Monthly with LBJ Article [4 Copies], January 2008 (Box 1930, Folder 8-9)
  - "Bios by JTD" (Box 1930, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts of Various Interviews (Box 1930, Folder 11)
  - Back-Up Discs of Interviews, Word Documents, Swanson Novel (Box 1930, Folder 12)
  - "Billy Bob's/Beat Rodeo" (Box 1930, Folder 13)
  - "Statesmen Copy", 2007 (Box 1930, Folder 14)
  - "Statesmen Copy", 2005 (Box 1930, Folder 15)
  - "Articles", 2004 (Box 1930, Folder 16)
  - "2006 Statesman and Other Articles" (Box 1931, Folder 1)
  - "Statesman Articles", 2009 (Box 1931, Folder 2)
  - "2003 Articles, Some 2002 Articles Also" (Box 1931, Folder 3)
  - "Articles", 2002 (Box 1931, Folder 4)
  - Willie Nelson Biography for Island Records (Box 1931, Folder 5)
  - Biographies for Columbia Records Press and Publicity (Box 1931, Folder 6)
  - Biographies for Sugar Hill Records (Box 1931, Folder 7)
  - Bill and Bonnie Hearse Biography for Warner Bros. Records (Box 1931, Folder 8)
  - Other Biographies for Record Companies (Box 1931, Folder 9)
  - Proofs for Articles to Austin-American Statesmen (Box 1931, Folder 10)
  - Proofs for Jerry Jeff Walker's Great Gonzos CD (Box 1931, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Austin-American Statesmen Articles (Box 1931, Folder 12)
  - Austin Monthly, February and April 2010 (Box 1931, Folder 13)
  - "T's Articles"
    - "Kelly's College Letters, Wedding Records" (2 folders) (Box 1931, Folder 14-15)
    - "Terry's Writings Starting October 2, 1981" (2 folders) (Box 1931, Folder 16-17)
    - "John T. Davis Starting October 1987" (Box 1931, Folder 18)
    - "Old Terry's Writings, Report Cards, Old Letters" (Box 1931, Folder 19)
    - Early Articles as a Music Critic in Austin (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1931, Folder 20)
    - Early Articles as a Music Critic in Austin (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1932, Folder 1)
    - "Kelly Murphy's Letters" (2 folders) (Box 1932, Folder 2-3)
  - Gloria Swanson Memoir
    - Garbo Proposal; Copy" (Box 1932, Folder 4)
    - Transcript of Interview with Fashion Houses (Box 1932, Folder 5)
    - Final Draft of A Visit from Gloria Swanson, 1983 (Box 1932, Folder 6)
    - Gloria Swanson at United Artists 1925-1933, Final Copy (Box 1932, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Gloria Swanson Memoir, Agust 1983 (Box 1932, Folder 8)
    - "Doe's Revision", December 1994 (Box 1932, Folder 9)
    - "Swanson" (Box 1932, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Doe Coover Agency, 1995 (Box 1932, Folder 11)
    - Research on Gloria Swanson (Box 1932, Folder 12)
    - Recordings of Daum's Notes on Swanson and Degas, 1993 (Box 1932, Folder 13)
  - Austin City Limits: 25 Years of American Music
    - Draft, 1993 (Box 1932, Folder 14)
    - 1 Copy, signed (Box 1932, Folder 15)
    - 1 Copy, unsigned (Box 1932, Folder 16)
    - PBS Promotional Photos for ACL, 1988 (Box 1932, Folder 17)
    - "Austin City Limits: Take Four" (Box 1932, Folder 18)
    - "Austin City Limits Light Up Sixth Season!" (Box 1932, Folder 19)
    - "Austin City Limits Premieres Season Seven" (Box 1932, Folder 20)
    - "Austin City Limits Premieres Eighth Season" (Box 1932, Folder 21)
    - "Austin City Limits Premieres Ninth Season" (Box 1932, Folder 22)
    - "Austin City Limits Celebrate Ten Years!" (Box 1932, Folder 23)
    - "Austin City Limits 12th Season" (Box 1932, Folder 24)
    - "Austin City Limits Premieres Season 13" (Box 1932, Folder 25)
    - "Press Release: Austin City Limits Premieres 14th Season on PBS" (Box 1932, Folder 26)
    - "Press Release: Austin City Limits' 15th Season Premieres on PBS" (Box 1932, Folder 27)
    - "Season Sixteen: General Press Release" (Box 1932, Folder 28)
    - "Austin City Limits Season 17" (Box 1932, Folder 29)
    - "Season 18 General Release" (Box 1932, Folder 30)
    - "Roy Clark with Clarence "Gatemouth" Brown #501" (Box 1933, Folder 1)
    - "Gary Morris Sylvia #1101" (Box 1933, Folder 2)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for Willie Nelson/Tracy Nelson" (Box 1933, Folder 3)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for Michael Murphy" (Box 1933, Folder 4)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for Norton Buffalo" (Box 1933, Folder 5)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for ACL #501-503, 505-513" (Box 1933, Folder 6)
    - "Michael Murphy #301" (Box 1933, Folder 7)
    - "Willie Nelson/Tracy Nelson #201" (Box 1933, Folder 8)
    - "Austin City Limits Satellite Schedule", 1999 (Box 1933, Folder 9)
    - "The Music for Austin City Limits VI" (Box 1933, Folder 10)
    - "Season 21: Sagebrush Symphony" (Box 1933, Folder 11)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for Austin City Limits #101-113" (Box 1933, Folder 12)
    - "KLRU Contact Mary Sullivan" (Box 1933, Folder 13)
    - "Austin City Limits' 20th" (Box 1933, Folder 14)
    - "Austin City Limits' 20th", 1994 (Box 1933, Folder 15)
    - "Austin City Limits" (Box 1933, Folder 16)
    - Music Row Magazine, April/May and September/October Issues, 1998 (Box 1933, Folder 17)
    - "Legends", January 26, 1999 (Box 1933, Folder 18)
    - Proposed Forward to ACL Book and Interview with Lyle Lovett (Box 1933, Folder 19)
    - "ACL Staff Questionnaire" (Box 1933, Folder 20)
    - "Season 19: Roseanne Cash/Carlene Carter #1901" (Box 1933, Folder 21)
    - Email Correspondence with Terry Lickona, 1999 (Box 1933, Folder 22)
    - Book Outline (Box 1933, Folder 23)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for #1201-1210" (Box 1933, Folder 24)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheets for ACL #1301-1311 Open and Close" (Box 1933, Folder 25)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheets for ACL #1401 George Strait—#1414" (Box 1933, Folder 26)
    - "ACL 23 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #2301-2313" (Box 1933, Folder 27)
    - "ACL 20 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #2001-2013" (Box 1933, Folder 28)
    - "ACL 21 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #2101-2113" (Box 1933, Folder 29)
    - "ACL 22 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #2201-2213" (Box 1933, Folder 30)
    - "ACL 18 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #1801-1812" (Box 1933, Folder 31)
    - "ACL 19 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #1901-1913" (Box 1933, Folder 32)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for #701-714" [2 Copies] (Box 1933, Folder 33)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for #801-813" (Box 1933, Folder 34)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet #901-913" (Box 1933, Folder 35)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for #1001-1013" (Box 1933, Folder 36)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for #1601-1613" (Box 1933, Folder 37)
    - "ACL 17 PBS Music Cue Sheet for #11701-1713" (Box 1933, Folder 38)
    - "PBS Music Cue Sheet for #1101-1113" (Box 1933, Folder 39)
    - "ACL Contacts" (Box 1933, Folder 40)
    - Season 24's Introduction Speeches (Box 1933, Folder 41)
    - Editorial Comments from Texas Highways, 1999 (Box 1934, Folder 1)
    - "Season 18 Interviews" (Box 1934, Folder 2)
    - "Season 19 Interviews" (Box 1934, Folder 3)
    - "Season 20 Interviews" (Box 1934, Folder 4)
    - "Season 21 Interviews" (Box 1934, Folder 5)
    - "ACL Artist's Questionnaire" (Box 1934, Folder 6)
    - Additional ACL Staff Questionnaires (Box 1934, Folder 7)
    - PBS ACL Newspaper, 1999 (Box 1934, Folder 8)
    - Assorted ACL Documents (Box 1934, Folder 9)
    - Membership CD Packages (Box 1934, Folder 10)
    - Collection of ACL Festival Music, 2003 (Box 1934, Folder 11)
    - "Terry/Scott" Cassette Tapes, November 23, 1998 (Box 1934, Folder 12)
    - "Bill Arhos" Cassette Tape, November 1998 (Box 1934, Folder 13)
    - "ACL Staff Interviews" (Box 1934, Folder 14)
    - Official Season Program, 2010 (Box 1934, Folder 15)
    - Notes and Booklet on The Austin City Limits Experience (Box 1934, Folder 16)
    - "Austin City Limits: Horizon Unlimited" Draft, 2004 (Box 1934, Folder 17)
    - "ACL Biz Stories" (Box 1934, Folder 18)
    - "Newspaper & Magazine Clips" (Box 1934, Folder 19)
    - Austin City Limits Exhibition Pamphlets (Box 1934, Folder 20)
    - "ACL Catalog Material" (Box 1934, Folder 21)
    - 1st ACL Fest, 2002 (Box 1934, Folder 22)
    - ACL Fest, 2003 (Box 1934, Folder 23)
    - ACL Festival, 2005 (Box 1935, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks from ACL, 2005 and 2008 (Box 1935, Folder 2)
    - ACL (2 folders), 2007 (Box 1935, Folder 3-4)
    - ACL, 2009 (Box 1935, Folder 5)
    - Drafts of Chapters from ACL Book (Box 1935, Folder 6)
    - Drafts of Chapters #2-10 of ACL Book (Box 1935, Folder 7)
    - Promotional Photographs by KLRN PBS (Box 1935, Folder 8)
    - "ACL Staff Tapes" [4 Tapes], November 1998 (Box 1935, Folder 9)
    - Austin City Limits by Clifford Endres [2 Copies, Inlaid Material] (Box 1935, Folder 10)
    - "ACL Artist Interviews" (2 folders) (Box 1935, Folder 1)
    - ACL, 2008 (Box 1935, Folder 2)
    - "ACL Copy" (Box 1935, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Pamphlets by KLRU (Box 1935, Folder 4)
    - "Season 19" Artist Profiles (Box 1935, Folder 5)
    - "Season 22" Artist Profiles (Box 1935, Folder 6)
    - "Season 18" Artist Profiles (Box 1935, Folder 7)
    - Other ACL Material (Box 1935, Folder 8)
    - "ACL Draft" and "Transcript Apps #4", February 3, 1999 (Box 1935, Folder 9)
    - "Willie [Nelson] Re: ACL; Bruce Hornsby 12-5", December 3, 1998 (Box 1935, Folder 10)
    - Mary Beth Rogers KLRU", January 12, 1998 (Box 1935, Folder 11)
    - "Emmie [Lou Harris] 1-14-99" and "Bonnie Raitt] 12-9-98" and "Lyle [Lovett] 12-21" (Box 1935, Folder 12)
    - Artist Profiles by KRLU (Box 1935, Folder 13)
    - Austin City Limits Artist Pictures by KRLU (Box 1935, Folder 14)
    - Austin City Limits Official Programs, 2008 and 2010 (Box 1935, Folder 15)
    - Assorted ACL Materials (Box 1935, Folder 16)
    - Artist Reviews, May 2005 (Box 1935, Folder 17)
    - "ACL Book" (Box 1935, Folder 18)
    - "Austin City Limits: The First Decade" Draft (Box 1935, Folder 19)
    - Austin City Limits: 25 Years of American Music Book Outline (Box 1935, Folder 20)
    - Mock Book Covers, May 2005 (Box 1935, Folder 21)
    - Notes on Austin City Limits: 25 Years of Music (Box 1935, Folder 22)
    - Draft of "Chapter Eleven" (Box 1935, Folder 23)
  - South by Southwest (SXSW), 1987-2010
    - 1987 (Box 1937, Folder 1)
    - 1988 (Box 1937, Folder 2)
    - 1989 (Box 1937, Folder 3)
    - 1990 (Box 1937, Folder 4)
    - 1991 (Box 1937, Folder 5)
    - 1992 (Box 1937, Folder 6)
    - 1993 (Box 1937, Folder 7)
    - 1994 (Box 1937, Folder 8)
    - Official Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1937, Folder 9)
    - 1996 (Box 1937, Folder 10)
    - Official Media Guide, 1997 (Box 1937, Folder 11)
    - Official Media Guide, 1998 (Box 1937, Folder 12)
    - Official Media Guide, 1999 (Box 1937, Folder 13)
    - Other SXSW material (Box 1937, Folder 14)
    - Celebrate Austin: A Guide to the City and the Texas Hill Country (Box 1937, Folder 15)
    - The Best of No Depression: Writing About American Music (Box 1937, Folder 16)
    - Willie Nelson: Revolutions of Time…The Journey CD (Box 1937, Folder 17)
    - Don't Mess With Texas Music, Volume 3 CD (Box 1938, Folder 1)
    - Antone's Home of the Blues DVD (Box 1938, Folder 2)
    - Kerrville Folk Festival Songbooks (Box 1938, Folder 3)
    - Various Music Festival Catalogs (Box 1938, Folder 4)
    - New Orleans Jazz and Heritage Festival, 2005 (Box 1938, Folder 5)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 1988-1989 (Box 1938, Folder 6)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 1990-1991 (Box 1938, Folder 7)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 1992 (Box 1938, Folder 8)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 1993-1994 (Box 1938, Folder 9)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 1995-1996 (Box 1938, Folder 10)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2001-2002 (Box 1938, Folder 11)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2003 (Box 1938, Folder 12)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2004-2005 (Box 1938, Folder 13)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2005-2006 (Box 1938, Folder 14)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2006-2007 (Box 1939, Folder 1)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2007 (Box 1939, Folder 2)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2009-2010 (Box 1939, Folder 3)
    - SXSW Catalogs, 2011 (Box 1939, Folder 4)
    - ACL Pocket Guides [8 Copies], 2008 (Box 1939, Folder 5)
    - ACL Pocket Guides [7 Copies], 2010 (Box 1939, Folder 6)
    - Various SXSW Pocket Guides (Box 1939, Folder 7)
    - "Kerrville Awards" (Box 1939, Folder 8)